And what else do we have?
We can also add up reference images.
So what reference images are is basically images
that we can add in order to either include
in the generated result or inspire the bot.
So for example, let's say that we want to create
an image, similar to another image that we already have,
or we've seen somewhere.
We can just add that image over here, upload it over here.
And it will be used as a reference image.
Or for example, we want to add a certain logo
of our company in the generated image in a certain part, right?
So we can use this reference image part
in order to give the AI bot our photo.
And that photo will be used when it comes to generating
the end result that we want.
So this is also reference images.
We can click on Upload Image.
And we can add our reference images over here, close this one.